<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yael&#39;s weird Blog</title>
    <link>http://ariael21.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yael&#39;s weird Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 23:41:18 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ariael21.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 - THILOS BLOG: Going Home</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/thilo-going-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 23:41:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/thilo-going-home/</guid>
      <description>Travel Horrors Thilo Didnt know that he was about to witness some travel horrors on the ferry, which included dogs, children and CATS on board in the sleeping area.
I did sleep quite good under the circumstances though! I only had to use the bathroom once during the night, under the steady eyes of the only other creature awake on the ferry; THE CAT WAS STALKING ME!
The ferry was supposed to board in Livorno at 2pm, thus i scheduled my train reservations for the train leaving at 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - Cefalu</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:07:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-11/</guid>
      <description>Cefalu In the morning we got to realise that we missed the train heading to Cefalu at around 10 AM while the next one was going to depart at 3 PM. After some rather uncomfortable discussions with our AirBnB host, who also happened to rent cars and scooters, we decided to stay at the beach until 2 pm and catch the train at 3.
To get to the train station, we had to walk for over 30 minutes in the midday sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - We&#39;re Open Water Divers!</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 23:07:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-10/</guid>
      <description>We are now Open Water Divers! A rainy morning After we got up we immediately checked the phone for Alans message to find out if we could finish our diving course despite the weather conditions. When we saw that he hadn&amp;rsquo;t informed us yet we pictured the diving crew in our heads huddling together discussing if they could dare to make the dive. As it turned out they had already decided an hour ago to do it and the reason we didn&amp;rsquo;t get the Okay from Alan was that he had overslept, lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - THILOS BLOG Part 3</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-10-thilo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 16:35:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-10-thilo/</guid>
      <description>In the morning I accidently cross one of Catanias local Saturday-morning-markets where I buy fruits and bread. I felt really local lol.
I arrive in Taormina before lunch, where I meet the mess left behind by the other peasants who supposedly already checked out. Our host allowed us to leave our baggage BUNDLED at one spot in the apartment so that the cleaning lady could clean around our stop. To my surprise all bags were distributed along the whole flat + all of our food was still chilling in the fridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 - Blue Sea Tribe</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:07:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-9/</guid>
      <description>Scuba Diving day 2 Cold water Still not being able to figure out the bus timetable Yael, Samira and Timo said goodbye to Thilo (who was going to have his own crazy adventures that day) and took a taxi to the diving center where the blood hungry moscitos (and our diving instructors of course) were already waiting for our arrival. We then had to carry our diving equipment up to a hotel (lucky for us, someone had already brought up the heavy air bottles) and went diving in the hotel&amp;rsquo;s swimming pool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 - THILOS BLOG Part 2</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-9-thilo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 16:34:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-9-thilo/</guid>
      <description>Syrakus, Ortigia &amp;amp; Catania Being left alone again, I&amp;rsquo;m taking the train going to Syrakus so that i can visit the Island of Ortigia. I planned on renting a scooter, but apparently it was going to rain so I thought it best to take the train ride instead. I arrive in Syrakus at around lunchtime, upon where I immediately digest my sandwiches that I prepared back home. It&amp;rsquo;s suppper hot again, I felt like i was melting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8: Scuba Diving in Taormina</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:56:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-8/</guid>
      <description>Scuba Diving in Taormina The whole gang wakes up early as the practical diving course starts at 9 AM! We take a taxi as the bus only appears like 5x a day like tf.
Arriving early in front of the diving shop, we descend to the closely located bay in front of the Isola Bella, one of the most important attractions of the city. Here, Thilo takes a bath under the jealous eyes from his companions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 - THILOS BLOG Part 1</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-8-thilo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 16:33:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-8-thilo/</guid>
      <description>Thilo exploring Taormina [Morning with group in Post &amp;ldquo;Day 8&amp;rdquo;]
After getting rid of his peasants, Thilo celebrates his newly gained freedom by exploring the Isola Bella itself. The island counted as private property until the early 90s, whose owner pimped the whole island to the max. There are several houses and pools located on the small island, all of them perfectly blending into the islands rocky nature. I decided to ignore some stop signs standing in front of some of the paths which eventually led me to the very top of the island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7: How to miss a train - for dummies</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 22:10:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-7/</guid>
      <description>Neapel - Taormia How to miss a train - for dummies After again drinking too much witch juice the evening before, we all wake up feeling fine af (the usual). For breakfast we get served compact cracker-müesli with a few drops of milk (why do we always forget to go shopping though?!). Soon we realise that we still need to pack, clean and shower the hangover away, all within not even an hour before the train departs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6: Ischia beach day</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:48:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-6/</guid>
      <description>Ischia After (again) going to bed way too late the evening before, we chose to let the ferry go that we planned on catching at 08.40 and to take the next one which departed shortly before 11am. Obviously, we still had to rush as we nearly missed this ferry too. we still made it though #hatersgonnahate
While the ferry was arriving in Ischia (the main city on Ischia the Island), the speakers announced that the next stop was going to be Forio, a town on the other side of the island, where we planned on going to anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5: Pompeii</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 18:05:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Pompeii After arriving late at night the day before, we decided to sleep out in the morning as we all felt a lil ded inside. We ended up brunching at around 12.
Todays Program: Pompeii! After doing some research &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; found out that there&amp;rsquo;s a bus going to Pompeii starting from the harbour. On our way to the harbour, we saw some relly nice vintage shops! We had to hurry to catch the buses though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4: Neapel, boat tour on Capri and a swim in the Blue Grotto</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 08:56:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Florence - Napoli Feeling fresh after a shitty sleep at night, we headed to the train station to reach the next city on our list: Napoli. After some espresso shots we felt alive enough to start the next journey. In the train we did some actual productive work. :pog:
Samira - the next premium LinAlg TA - worked for about 2 minutes and continued to take a juicy nap. Get ready erstis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3: Even more Florence and a nice vintage shop</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 08:52:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Cathedral After planning to get up early to go check out another camera store the day before, we decided to stay in bed for as long as possible in the morning. The cathedral was, as we thought, going to open at around 10am. We then thought it to be best to get to the church shortly before the opening to avoid the huge queues that we witnessed the day before. Turns out that there were already hundreds of people + the church opened at 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2: Exploring Florence</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 08:51:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Florence Early Morning; Surprisingly, the only person to experience some sort of hangover was Timo; the rest of us dealt quite well with the alcohol overload from the evening before. We then (obviously) brunched (cereals) and then headed for the city. We tried to get into the cathedral, however the queue was long enough to shoo us away. We then decided to check out the cathedral on the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1: Arth-Goldau to Florence</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 08:30:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Start of our journey Arth-Goldau to Florence General Please ignore all spelling errors or weird sentence structure. English is not our first language. But we hope you can enjoy our blog posts nonetheless! :D
 Text and images are by Thilo, Samira, Timo and Yael Cameras: Fujifilm XT-4, GoPro Hero 7 Silver  Introduction First, let us introduce our group! We are four people:
   Samira Timo Thilo Yael            Arth-Goldau: Departure at 8:18 We left at 8:18 from Arth-Goldau with our big booty backpacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
