<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yael&#39;s weird Blog</title>
    <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yael&#39;s weird Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:05:40 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ariael21.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:05:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Pompeii [we will add images later to this post. Sowy guys]
Because we were so dead from the last few days we decided to sleep longer. We got up at about 12 and had brunch.
A little later we got ready and went out into the city. We walked through the city and saw some nice vintage shops but we had to hurry to catch our bus. We bought all our tickets last minute and ran into the bus to Pompeii.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 08:56:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Florence - Napoli Feeling fresh after a shitty sleeps at night, we headed to the train station to reach the next city on our list: Napoli. After some espresso shots we felt alive enough to start the next journey. In the train we did some actual productive work. :pog:
Samira - the next premium LinAlg TA - worked for about 2 minutes and continued to take a juicy nap. Get ready erstis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 08:52:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Cathedral After planning to get up early to go check out another camera store the day before, we decided to stay in bed for as long as possible in the morning. The cathedral was, as we thought, going to open at around 10am. We then thought it to be best to get to the church shortly before the opening to avoid the huge queues that we witnessed the day before. Turns out that there were already hundreds of people + the church opened at 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 08:51:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Florence Early Morning; Surprisingly, the only person to experience some sort of hangover was Timo; the rest of us dealt quite well with the alcohol overload from the evening before. We then (obviously) brunched (cereals) and then headed for the city. We tried to get into the cathedral, however the queue was long enough to shoo us away. We then decided to check out the cathedral on the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 08:30:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ariael21.github.io/posts/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Start of our journey Arth-Goldau to Florence Remark: Please ignore all spelling errors or weird sentence structure :kekw: English is not our first language. But we hope you can enjoy our blog posts nonetheless! :D
Introduction First, let us introduce our group! We are four people:
   Samira Timo Thilo Yael            Arth-Goldau: Departure at 8:18 We left at 8:18 from Arth-Goldau with our big booty backpacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
